♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
‪["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
[Atoy] Where are the children?
Give me back the children!
I'll make these kids suffer.
I'll profit from them.
[Velma] That's Red's child, right?
Or maybe you're your father's spy?
Why did my parents turn out like that?
Good thing you didn't take
after your parents.
[Atoy] We need to know where they
could have taken the children.
V. Starts with a V.
Ve-- Velora Bay!
It's in the classified data!
I need the laptop.
[Atoy] That's a huge place. Where is that?
[Lily, in English] It's posing
as a high-end beach resort,
but it's actually one
of the big concentration camps of…
the terrorist group Obsidian.
[in English] That's the international
human trafficking syndicate.
[in English] Yes. One and only.
Who owns that island?
[Mercado] That is Mr. Edison Kalaf,
the owner of Velora Bay.
He has a club here that he often visits
at this time of the year.
[Atoy] Where is this club?
I want to go there.
[Trinity, in English]
This is a special event.
Okay, where groups will battle
in drag performances.
[in English] The winners will be invited
to perform
at Mr. Edison Kalaf's 60th birthday bash.
[Atoy] Do you know how to dance?
[Paldo] Dance? Like this?
Why, 'Toy? What are you planning?
[Atoy] We'll perform.
But we need to go all out.
Really all out so we'll win.
Fabulous!
Will they torture us? Kill us? Like that?
Don't think about that.
[Atoy] Attach this to Trinity's collar,
Kalaf's assistant.
- [Emerson] What is this?
- [Atoy] Listening device.
[Trinity] The usual, the shipment
will be in transit from Velora Bay.
Which are women and young children.
You're really bratty even here, huh?
You need your tongue cut off.
- [grunts]
- [Ibyang sobs]
I'm your niece! We're family!
Family isn't about being related by blood.
Your mother infuriates me.
Especially when I see you!
‪PREVIOUSLY
[music swells]
[music fades]
Is it done?
It's done. You seem in a hurry.
I just want to go to church.
They're already there.
You know, Karla, I just noticed.
Why do you and Gavin seem allergic
to each other? Aren't you friends?
He's just avoiding me
because he thinks… we're already together.
- [sneaky music playing]
- Hey. I didn't know that, ah.
You're fast, faster than me even.
Come here, give me a kiss.
Hey! Stop that!
- [chuckles]
- Do you want me to cut your lips?
- Come on.
- [music continues]
I thought we were together?
[in English] So, okay. Let me guess.
[sneaky music playing]
You probably told Gavin
we're together because…
you know he likes you.
But he has a girlfriend.
Of course, you're hurt now.
You don't want to show him you're hurt…
so you said we're together.
Mm-hmm.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You talk too much.
[music continues]
You know…
just choose me instead.
Hey! No way!
[music fades]
So, you're semi-rejecting me now, huh?
But fine. That's okay.
It's okay with me.
I'll go along with it, maybe…
you know?
You'll develop feelings for me.
- [scoffs] Dream on, Uno.
- Ouch.
You two are so ambiguous, huh?
You're both petty, huh?
- [upbeat music]
- The children are missing,
and you still can't be honest
with yourselves.
[scoffs] So petty.
[upbeat music playing]
Right?
[music fades]
- [sewing machine whirring]
- [theme music starts]
[theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
- [scratches]
- [snipping]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
- [thumps & gunshots]
- [music intensifies]
[clicking]
[snipping]
- [music swells]
- [electronic blipping]
[music fades]
[muffled chatter in the distance]
[sensual funky music playing]
[music continues]
- [music fades]
- Hello, ladies!
What's your group's name?
Us?
[in English] Oh, we are the…
[all] Karayom Kweens!
Oww!
So, it's you.
Uh-huh, mm-hmm.
[in English] I'm the leader,
slash, choreographer
of The Glitter…
- Bombz!
- Oh!
The three-peat champion
of the Reyna Royale Rumble.
[in English] And you are?
- Me?
- Mmm.
I'm Antonia.
[in English] Leader, slash,
costume designer.
And your name is?
[sneaky music playing]
Chiquita?
[music continues]
Velma!
You know each other?
[muffled chatter in distance]
Very well!
She used to be my and Bunda's BFF!
But because she stole my makeup kit
and I couldn't perform,
we've been FO forever!
[others] Oh!
Well, I only did that
because you stole my boyfriend.
You're a snake!
[others gasp]
Ay, you're crazy.
I didn't steal anything from you,
because I'm prettier than you!
[jeering]
And it really came from you, huh.
Wait. What are you doing here?
"No pets allowed" here, right?
- Oh.
- [Chiquita] And…
maybe you're just stalking me.
And why would I do that, huh?
Are you special?
[laughs]
[Nestor] Oh, uh-- Uh, Chi… Chiquita, uh,
Velma is our choreographer.
She's not our pet.
[others] Ohh!
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, you won't win.
Amateurs like you
will never take our crown.
Says who?
And mark that on your ugly foreheads!
- [others] Oh!
- [Chiquita] Come on, girls!
It's suffocating here.
- [Atoy] Ay, ay!
- [playful music playing]
- [Nestor] It stinks here!
- [Atoy] Ay, ay.
Crazy. It's really dusty, huh?
[gasps]
[Nestor] You're crazy!
That's crazy, huh. Not even good yet.
That's them.
That's the Glitter Bombz.
I saw their dance performances, they
are really amazing. They own the killer…
death drop!
They're really trained in dance,
they're very good.
Atoy, we'll lose to them.
Exactly, I watched them.
They're really good, eh.
How do we beat them, right?
No matter what, we need to beat them.
Correct.
We can do it!
[Nestor] Huh?
Don't worry. I got you.
[playful music playing]
Because we are the…
[all] Karayom Kweens!
[music fades]
♪ Don't rush the feelings ♪
♪ Of my heart ♪
♪ That's no stranger to this ♪
- ♪ And always at stake… ♪
Oh! Here it is, guys!
[in English] Your food and drinks!
Courtesy of Brother Kurt!
Thank you, Brother Kurt!
[in English] Thank you, Kurt.
[in English] Oh! Gavin. I watched
Cathy's latest vlog, it was ah…
something like breaking up
or getting over heartbreak and uh…
Was that about you? Or… Did you break up?
[in English] Yes. A few days ago.
Ah, why didn't you tell me?
Why do I need to tell you?
Why care about our relationship?
Don't you have a boyfriend?
Oh! Karla, you have a boyfriend? Who?
Why didn't you tell me, Gavin?
Didn't I act as a bridge
between you and Cathy?
And now I find out
from someone else that you broke up?
What? Surprise?
[Gavin] What's your problem?
Well, you surprised us
when you and Uno got together.
You didn't even tell me you liked him.
Oh, Gavin, it's like…
Why are you angry at Karla?
No.
[in English] Look. I'm okay,
and I'm happy for her.
I'm moving on from Cathy.
Actually, I'm already dating someone, eh.
[Gavin] I'll just go out, ah.
[music continues]
[in English] Karla, I, ah…
I thought you liked Gavin, so…
Why Uno?
Eh, please, Brother Kurt. Don't meddle.
Sorry, huh. I'm not meddling.
["Sa Wala" by Wickermoss
with Neth Macam playing]
Aww. Babe, I miss you too.
[footsteps tapping]
- You can join.
- [clears throat] Chiquita,
let's talk.
[in English] Talk to the hand.
You annoy me!
Uhm, Chiquita, uh, let me be honest.
You know, there are more important things,
bigger things than your fight with Velma.
Be direct with me. What do you need?
Um…
there are missing children,
and we suspect
they were taken to Velora Bay.
Where your boss' birthday will be held.
That's why we need
to win this contest, to get there.
This is the only way we found.
So, what is this?
[in English] Game fixing?
We'll perform badly just for you?
[clears throat] Chiquita, listen. Okay?
We know your group
is more experienced than ours,
and we don't intend to take your crown.
But, please.
Children's lives are at stake here!
[Emerson] Yes. And also…
we're not after the prize.
We can give you the prize in full.
If that's-- if that's what you want.
And besides, girl, you know me.
You know I wouldn't talk to you
if it wasn't important, right?
So please, cooperate.
Mmm? Do you want proof?
- All right.
- Oh.
[Velma] Here are the pictures
of the missing children, oh.
They're cute, right?
Oh. They're really cute, huh?
One even looks like my niece.
Mmm, right?
All we want is to return them
to their parents.
Aww.
In fairness…
- You tell stories well, huh?
- [tense music]
[Chiquita] You even have these stories
about kidnappings of children.
I don't believe you.
No. What I'm saying is true.
Oh, no.
I won't be swayed
by your pity effect, huh.
And you have the nerve to approach me.
Here's the deal. Let's put it this way.
May the best drag group win.
Unfortunately, that's not you.
Step aside.
[tense music playing]
We can't do anything.
[in English] No choice…
It seems we really have no choice but…
superbly slay this contest.
- [music fades]
- That's it.
[upbeat music]
Hey.
[upbeat music continues]
[upbeat dance music]
[music ends]
[in English] Hello, hello!
Hello, queens, divas, gays,
and all allies!
[in English] Welcome, welcome, welcome!
Tonight, the spotlight
is hotter than your ex's DMs.
- [audience] Ohh! Yes!
- Because…
this is the fiercest, loudest,
and the most fabulous
drag showdown of the year,
the Reyna Royale Rumble!
[audience cheering]
Before anything else, I would like
to thank each and every one of you
- for making this competition possible.
- [upbeat music]
[audience applauding]
So, before I judge the competition,
I would like to hand this mic
to our host for tonight.
Please welcome, Tiny!
- [audience cheering]
- [music continues]
Hi! Mmm.
[smooches] Oh, do your best. Okay?
Thank you very much, Boss Trina!
Let's give her
a round of applause, everyone!
- [audience cheering]
- And of course,
let's not delay any longer!
I know everyone is ready!
Is it okay to hear your applause
with screams?
[audience cheering]
Whoops! Here it is!
Let's welcome to the stage…
the Glitter Bombz!
- [audience cheering]
- [upbeat music playing]
Reigning champ, reigning champ.
- [audience applauding]
- [music continues]
[audience applauding]
[music continues]
[audience cheering]
They're good.
[music continues]
[Tiny, in English] Thank you so much,
Glitter Bombz!
Make some noise for Glitter Bombz!
Here it is! The act
that will tear down the stage!
The powerhouse performance!
Let's give it up for
- Velvet and Vixens!
- [audience applauding]
- [cool upbeat music playing]
- [audience whooping]
[music continues]
[audience cheering]
[Tiny, in English] Thank you so much,
Velvet and Vixens!
Ah, they're newcomers.
But they really showed
something different.
[in English] Congratulations in advance,
Velvet and Vixens!
Now, could this next one…
really pass through the eye of the needle?
- [audience cheering]
- Could this be
the international performance level?
Come on! Let's welcome to the stage…
The Karayom Kweens!
- [audience cheering]
- [upbeat music playing]
[audience cheering]
[music continues]
[audience whooping]
[audience clapping]
[audience whoops]
- [audience whoops]
- [music continues]
[laughing]
- [audience cheering]
[music continues]
[music fades]
[audience applauding]
[Tiny] Once again, the Karayom Kweens!
[in English] Very good!
[upbeat music]
Looks like we'll have a tough time.
[music continues]
[in English] So, are you guys excited?
[audience cheering] Yes!
Excited, Glitter Bombz?
- [exclaims]
- Excited, Karayom Kweens?
Here are our top two contenders.
They got the highest scores,
and they will battle
for the Reyna Royale crown!
[in English] We have, of course…
The Glitter Bombz!
[audience cheering]
And the challengers, the newcomers…
the Karayom Kweens!
[audience cheering]
[Trinity] And this is the moment
we've all been waiting for.
[audience cheering]
Okay? Here it is.
[in English]
With a jaw-breaking score of 92.7…
[audience cheering]
Oh, my god! I'm so nervous!
- [audience cheering]
- [Trinity laughing]
- [music swells]
- [Atoy] Give this to us, Lord.
I just want my children back.
I just want a chance
to rebuild our family.
[music fades]
- [electronic blipping]
- [intense music playing]
[music fades]
- [dramatic music]
- Watch him.
[in English] He might try to infiltrate
Velora Bay.
[in English] Don't worry, sir.
No undesirables have entered
Boss K's island yet.
[Trinity] If he shows up,
he will be dead on the spot.
[Mercado] Two access points.
Via helicopter, via boat. Padua,
their lives are in your hands.
I'll take care of them, sir.
I'll make sure they're ready.
Remember, huh. We are the main event
and also the main distraction,
so we need to do our best.
‪UP NEXT
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor, holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias